我们走出美食厨房
And as we make our way out of the gourmet kitchen,
回到客厅温暖的怀抱
we find ourselves way back in the warm embrace of the parlor.
放松 公爵夫人
Easy, dutches.
一间屋子而已 又不是高斯福德庄园
It's just one room, not Gosford Park .
你们从哪儿弄来这么好看的家具
Where'd you get all this sweet furniture?
我们租的 好让家里显得更舒适温馨一点
We rented it to make the house feel more comfortable and inviting.
别坐那儿 天呐
Don't sit there! Oh, my gosh.
我刚花了20分钟才把这褶皱弄好
It took me 20 minutes to get these chops just right.
好了 现在看着直吗
There. Does that look straight?
怎么看都不"直"
Nothing about that looks straight.
我好喜欢这房子 太美了
I love the house. It's beautiful.
送你们一棵小树
Here is a tree.
这是马拉巴栗
It's a pachira,
在台湾人心中象征着财运
a taiwanese symbol of good financial fortune.
所以也被称作发财树
So it's also known as a money tree.
我也是棵"摇钱树"
That makes two of us.
我提议大家共同举杯
Well, I would like to propose a toast.
我空了
Missed me.
感谢克莱尔和卡梅隆的辛勤付出
To the hard work of Claire and Cameron--
我也喜欢叫他们"克莱梅隆"
Or as I like to call them, "Clameron",
未来买家看到这房子时
which is what potential home buyers will be doing
就会这样
when they see this place.
"客来猛要"
Clamoring.
-房客来了猛要 -菲尔 别解释了
- Clamoring t-to buy it f-- - Phil, don't go back for it.
因为这座房子一定会大卖的
Because this house is going to sell.
镇上最厉害的房产经纪人是谁
Who's the best realtor in town?
-格尔·索普 -没错
- Gil Thorpe. - That's right,
-明天下午他会带客户过来 -没错
- And he has buyers coming over tomorrow. - That's right.
太好了
All right.
敬克莱尔和小卡
To Claire and Cam.
我姐姐和我爱人
My sister. My partner.
我姐姐 我爱人 我姐姐 我爱人
My sister! My partner! My sister! My partner!
-《唐人街》中的笑话 -还是空的
- "Chinatown." hilarious. - Still empty.
你知道我得坐你的车吧
Okay, you know you're my ride.
-敬克莱梅隆 -干杯 干杯
- To Clameron! - Hear, hear.
请发言
Speech!
天呐 我没有准备
Oh! Well, gosh, I wasn't prepared for this.
我 我们衷心感谢哪些
I...I think we should just really thank the people--
-感谢这次的优秀装修团队 -好吧
- Here's to the best construction crew in the business. - Okay. Okay.
汉克 路易斯以及帕克
Hank. Luis. Paco!
你要是也在就好了 伙计
Wish you could be here right now, buddy.
怎么 他死了吗
What? Did he die?
没有 他在屋顶上修理
No, he's on the roof fixing the shingle
本来第一次就该弄好的木瓦
that he should've gotten right the first time.
我觉得最重要的人
I guess the most important people-
-然后敬我的爱人 -对
- And then to my partner. - Yes.
我的人生伴侣
My lifelong companion.
我的爱
My lovah.
好了 小卡
Okay, Cam.
他一直都反对这项工程
Who had his doubts about this project the whole time,
但在我最低谷的时候 也没对我说
And never, even in my darkest moment,
"我早就告诉过你了吧"
said "I told you so."
那很好 不然他就错了
Which is good because he would've been wrong.
真有爱
Very gracious.
我相信这房子一定一下子就能卖掉
And I'm sure that the house is gonna sell in no time.
太棒了 干杯 干杯
Great. Hear, hear!
我有个朋友也想买房子
Hey, I've got a friend who wants to buy a house.
也许我放学后能带他过来
Maybe I can show it to him after school.
如果他买了 得给我些佣金
Then if he buys it, I'd get the commission.
怎么样
What would that be?
真可爱
Adorable.
我说正经的 我才不可爱呢
I'm serious. And I'm not adorable.
我要留小胡子
I'm getting a mustache.
我现在学会字母表了[儿歌]
I know my a-b-c's.
我猜你一会儿没成为焦点就难受是吧
I guess things weren't about you for a second.
好了 别闹了
Okay, wrapping this up.
敬房地产史上最快售出的房子
To the fastest sale in real estate history.
没错 太棒了
Yes! Bravo!
说真的 跟空杯子碰杯会倒霉的
Seriously, it's bad luck to toast with an empty glass.
邓菲 跟你说实话吧
Dunphy, I'm not gonna lie to you.
你们这房子弄得很不错 我的客户想入手
You guys did a nice job on the house. My buyer wants in.
太好了 真是个好消息
Fantastic! That is great news!
我们刚开工的时候
You know, when we first got into this--
别扯闲篇了
the small talk's over.
这是我们的开价
Here's what we're prepared to offer.
你开玩笑呢吧
You're joking, right?
做房产我从不开玩笑
I don't joke about real estate.
我只拿高尔夫和墨西哥人开玩笑
I joke about golf and Mexicans.
不过没关系 我老婆就是墨西哥人
It's okay, though. I'm married to one.
我们不可能接受的
W-we're not gonna take this.
那房子才第一天上市
It's the first day on the market.
-我们甚至连保本都难 -接受吧
- We'd barely break even. - Take it.
不行
No.
-市场现在一落千丈 -没有
- The market's crashing! - Nuh-unh.
你已经泥足深陷了
You're in over your head.
你才泥足深陷呢
Maybe you're in over your head.
邓菲 听我说
Dunphy, listen to me.
过了这村 你会后悔的
If you pass up on this, you're gonna regret it.
我完全不懂"后悔"二字的意思
I don't know the meaning of the word "Regret."
来了 法式吐司配双层培根
Here we go. French toast, double bacon.
蛋白配无黄油烤面包片[蠢货]
Egg whites, dry toast.
该死
Damn it.
我跟你说吧 格尔
Let me tell you something, Gil.
你或许是很厉害
You may be top dog,
但是会后悔的人是你
but you're the one who's gonna have regrets,
因为这房子弹指一挥就能卖掉
'cause this house is gonna sell like... that.
今天又是一场空
That's it for today.
我们要老死在这房子里了
We're going to die in this house.
靠枕都不那么蓬松了
Oh, the pillows have lost their fluff.
靠枕不是问题所在
The pillows are not the problem!
没事 曼尼 那一会儿见
It's okay, Manny. I'll see you in a minute.
好 我会很礼貌很友好的 我保证
Yes, I'll be polite and I'll be nice. I promise.
我要杀了他
I'm going to kill him.
哈维尔这次又怎么了
What'd Javier do this time?
他和他儿子好不容易共度周末
His one big weekend alone with his son,
我才知道
and I just found out
他把他新搞上的姘头也带过来了
that he brought his latest bimbo along.
他总是这样
He always does this.
你还记得那次他带曼尼
You remember that time that he took Manny
和那个脱衣舞娘去钓鱼的事吗
and that stripper fishing?
记得 他们连鱼毛都没钓到[乳头]
Yeah. They barely got a nipple.
拜托 那很经典 我刚想到的
Come on. That was good. I just thought of that.
你闹够了没
Are you done?
我猜她一定很满意那根钓鱼"棍"
I bet she was comfortable with the pole.
我应该在说完"乳头"就闭嘴的
Ah. Should've quit after "Nipple."
雷诺怎么每晚说荤段子都不累啊
How does Leno do it night after night?
我也在想我每晚是怎么忍受你的
I was just wondering that about myself.
菲尔 拜托 告诉我们点好消息
Phil, please. Tell us that you have some good news.
情况有点复杂 因为我没有好消息
Well, it's complicated because I don't have good news,
不过我真心希望你们喜欢我
But I really want you guys to like me.
什么
What?
格尔·索普打电话来说有新买家
Gil thorpe called back with another offer,
但是比上一位出的价格低一万美元
But it was $10,000 lower than the last one.
低
Lower?
好极了 那真是好极了 好极了
Oh, that is perfect. That's just perfect.
你有什么想说的吗 米奇尔
Something you wanna say, Mitchell?
是吧 我早告诉过你吧
Yes. I told you so.
我警告过你会出现这种情况
I warned you this would happen.
我试图阻止 但你不听我的
I tried to stop it, but you wouldn't let me.
我对了 你错了
I was right, and you were wrong.
你生活在可笑的被甜言蜜语包围的幻境中
You live in this ridiculous candy-colored fantasy land.
我可比你聪明多了
I am so much smarter than you,
我没落井下石奚落你 真是憋死我了
and it is killing me not to rub your nose in it!
不是 我只是在思考而已
No. I'm just thinking.
好了 伙计们 我们得做点什么
Okay, guys, we have to do something.
我们不能再把这房子留在手上了
We can't carry this house for much longer.
小卡 你前期设计花了多少钱
Cam, what did you spend on staging?
让我想想 我不知道
Uh, let's see. I don't know.
你怎么可以不知道
How can you not know?!
因为我如饥似渴 所有东西又都那么好
Because I was hungry, and everything was so pretty.
我以为这个不算事儿
and I didn't think it would matter
因为谁会想到
because who could've guessed
我们到现在还不能把房子卖出去啊
we wouldn't have sold the house by now?
我
Me.
菲尔 你觉得能不能
Phil, do you think you can
让格尔·索普把价格提高到第一次报的价格
Get Gil Thorpe up to his original offer?
-怎么弄 -我不知道
- How? - I don't know.
你行的 拍他马屁 哄他开心
You could, uh, flatter him, stroke his ego.
不 他不会上当的 他太聪明了
No, he'd never fall for that. He's too smart.
亲爱的 如果说有谁能搞定 那只能是你了
But, honey, if anybody can pull it off, you can.
你做什么都很出色
You're so good at everything.
那倒没错
That is true.
我试试
I'll do it.
我们回来了
We're back!
我真不敢相信 你又带了个妞来
I cannot believe that again you brought a girl.
这次的女人又是干什么的
What is it this time?
调鸡尾酒的服务员吗
A cocktail waitress?
船模 还是脱衣舞娘
A boat show model? A stripper?
不是 那样我可就挣大钱了
No, then I could make real money.
我只是个博士而已
I'm just a PHD.
妈妈 这位是崔茜
Mom, this is Trish.
-歌洛莉亚 你好 -你好
- Gloria, hi. - Hi.
-杰 -你好
- Jay. - How do you do?
我听过很多关于你的事情
I have heard so much about you.
她在艺术博物馆工作
She works at the museum of art.
太酷了 我们在闭馆之后过去参观的
It was so cool. We got an after hours tour,
崔茜说可以开闪光灯给那些画拍照
and Trish said I could take flash pictures of the paintings.
不过别担心 我没照
But don't worry. I didn't.
真是松了一口气啊
That's a relief.
我还担心得被迫欣赏照片呢
I was afraid I was gonna have to look at 'em.
那么你是在博物馆工作啊
So you work at the museum?
不是 我只是董事会成员
Oh, no. I'm just on the board.
我负责佳士得拍卖行的艺术品和古董业务
I run the art and antiquities department at Christie's.
让我想想 我想用个什么词来着
Let me see. What is the word I am looking for?
有了 晴天霹雳
Oh, yes. Bam!
你们两个是怎么认识的
So how did you two meet?
我玩扑克时赢了一台车 可那台车自燃了
I won a car in a poker game, but it caught on fire,
于是那家伙给了我一幅画
so the guy gave me a painting.
我把画拿到拍卖行
I took it to the auction house,
弄来弄去 我赚了一大笔
Eh, ticky ticky, I made a big profit
不过我还是带走了一幅大师级的作品
but I still came home with a masterpiece.
他说的是她
He means her.
我可不可以说 你家儿子实在太棒了
May I tell you, you have a wonderful boy?
彬彬有礼 风度翩翩
So well-mannered and chivalrous.
他就好像是从盖恩丝博勒或者范戴克
It's like he leapt off the canvas
16世纪时的帆布肖像画里跳出来的似的
Of a 16th century portrait by Gainsborough or Van Dyke.
听听人家多有学识
Listen to that brain.
他们能留下来吃饭吗
Can they stay for dinner?
那得他们说了算 小乖乖
Well, that's up to them, papi.
我怎么会拒绝免费的晚餐呢
How can I turn down a free meal?
第一次总是最艰难的
First time's the hardest.
你觉得呢 我亲爱的
What do you say, my love?
我觉得我现在还不想和这个小家伙告别
Well, I'm not sure I'm ready to say good-bye to this guy yet.
不敢要让我留下来 我必须有所贡献
But I'll only stay if you let me contribute.
我还真带了一瓶超棒的82年的波尔多红酒
I did bring along a fabulous bottle of '82 bordeaux
原打算我们周末喝的
that we didn't get to this weekend.
那么好的酒 你想把曼尼带回家都行
For that, you can take Manny home.
瞧我每天得忍受什么样的人了吧
See what I have to put up with?
格尔
Gil!
我是菲尔·邓菲
Phil Dunphy.
我就知道你会吃回头草的
I knew you'd come slinking back!
伙计们
Hey, guys!
是邓菲 他屈服了 我就跟你们说吧
It's Dunphy. He's cavin'. What did I tell you?
跟你们说什么来着
What did I tell you, hey?
邓菲 我可以把你"玩弄"于鼓掌间
Oh, Dunphy, I can play you like a ukulele,
因为你又弱小又可口
'cause you're small and dainty.
格尔 我想跟你谈谈你的出价
Gil, I wanna talk to you about your offer.
我给你打住吧
Let me stop you right there.
接下来应该这样进行
This is how this is gonna go down.
首先 我会带你吃一顿精致的晚餐
First of all, I'm gonna take you out to a very nice dinner.
我会跟你亲密地聊天
I'm gonna talk really sweet to you.
接着 我会在火炉边将你扑倒
And then I'm gonna lay you down by the fire...
刚开始我会很温柔 然后
Oh. Slow at first, then...
如果你们是在讨论卖房子的事
If you guys are talking about the house,
我的朋友扎克还在找卖家
My friend Zack's still looking.
宝贝 14岁的孩子买不起房子的
Honey, 14-year-olds can't afford to buy houses.
他才不是14岁
He's not 14.
他是名程序员 在我们学校做志愿者
He's a software guy who volunteers at my school.
我们会大汗淋漓
We're gonna be sweating...
他是有收入的成年人吗
He's an adult with money?
他开的车比你的豪华
He drives a nicer car than you.
马上给我他的号码
Get me his number right now!
然后你就会回家
And then you're gonna go home
告诉所有人你去看电影了
and tell everybody you went to the movies,
但你我心知肚明
but you and I both know
你被我的"索"命鱼雷"射"中了
that you got thorpedoed.
你猜怎么着 格尔 我只是出于礼貌
Guess what, Gil. This was a courtesy call
告诉你 我有别的买家了
to tell you that I have another buyer.
现在你可以告诉你的买家
So you can tell your buyer that
你让他们错失了一套好房
you cost them a great house
就因为你骄傲"鸡"大 下"手"太狠
because you got cocky and overplayed your hand.
你就"邓"着感受"菲"一般的痛苦吧
Prepare to Phil the agony of Dun-feat.
姓和名都用上了
Both names!
虽然我不是你这样的艺术达人
Now I'm not an art expert like you,
但我还是在一家上好的维加斯赌场的画廊
but I did acquire this piece in a gallery
淘到了这个雕像
in one of the finer Vegas casinos.
你觉得如何
What do you think?
确实说明了一些东西
It does say something.
他以前会说话 在音盒还没坏的时候
He used to, before his little voice box broke.
他说"欢迎主人回家 今天不顺吗"
It said, "Welcome home, master. Rough day?"
又来
Again?
她让我把雕像放到阁楼 你一定难以置信吧
Would you believe she made me keep this in the attic?
歌洛莉亚 崔茜说这是艺术
Gloria, Trish says this is art.
梭罗怎么说来着
What was it Thoreau said?
"重要的不是眼中所见 而是心中所见"
"It's not what you look at that matters. It's what you see."
听到没
Hear that?
你错了
You were wrong.
继续说呀
Keep talking like that,
然后你就会知道 他的音盒怎么坏的
and you will find out how he lost his voice box.
-什么情况 -他名字叫巴克利
- What have we here? - His name's Barkley.
真是可爱呀
That's delightful.
才不可爱呢 可恶心了
It's not delightful. It's disgusting.
想想沃霍尔 想想昆斯
Uh, look at Warhol. Look at Koons.
很多当代艺术中伟大的作品
A lot of great works of contemporary art
最初都被误认为是垃圾
were initially dismissed as garbage.
说得太对了 崔茜
Excellent point, Trish.
这连垃圾都比不上
This is not even garbage.
没人愿意把它带走 太大装不进垃圾桶
They wouldn't take it. It's too big for the can.
我眼中的他外表是一个人 实质上却不算人
Now what I see is a man who is not man.
他是一位失去了尊严的仆人
He is a servant who has lost his dignity.
说的就是当今社会的阶级制度
It is a commentary on the class system in society--
不过把钥匙和太阳镜放他身上倒是很方便
As well as a handy place to put your keys and sunglasses.
不管他是什么
Whatever he is,
你的巴克利都要被扔进阁楼
your Barkley is going back to the attic.
我去看下宝宝
I'm going to see the baby.
巴克利
Barkley.
名字取得好
Very clever.
来吧 我们玩游戏去
Come on, guys. Let's play.
你们要玩什么
What are you going to play?
猜字游戏 我和崔茜对阵老爸和杰
Charades. Me and Trish against dad and Jay.
我不得不提醒你 杰 他俩很厉害
I have to warn you, Jay. These two are very good.
他们简直就像心有灵犀一般
It's like they have their own language.
我也要玩
I want to play, too.
我该加哪一队
Which team should I join?
-曼尼那队 -杰那队
- Go with Manny. - Go with Jay.
-跟他们 -去他们队
- Them. - His team.
好的 太棒了
Okay, then. Great.
那晚上见
Well, we'll see you tonight.
扎克·巴比确实是名成年人
well, Zack Barbie is indeed an adult,
他喜欢这个社区 很有兴趣
He likes the neighborhood, and he's interested.
感谢上帝
Oh, thank god.
不是吧你 是上帝把他介绍给你们的吗
Really? Did god come in here and tell you about him?
我可不记得有这回事
Because I don't remember it that way.
好啦 够啦 大家
Okay, okay, this is it, people.
我们可不能失去这个买家了
We cannot afford to lose this buyer.
我站起来干嘛
Why am I standing?
菲尔 你觉得这地方适合他吗
Phil, do you think this is the right house for him?
很难说 他年轻 单身
It's hard to tell. He's young. He's single.
其余的信息我就不知道了
I don't know anything else about him.
扎克·巴比 生于1986年
Zack Barbie. Born 1986.
去了一所叫"芝麻"的大学
Went to college at a place called "Mit."
MIT[麻省理工大学]
M.I.T.
我知道怎么拼
I know how to spell it.
五个单词
Five words.
是一本书
It's a book.
有位老人
There's an old man...
在船上
On the boat...
他捕了一条大鱼
He caught a big fish.
《老人和鱼》
The old man and the fish!
时间到
Uh, time!
是《老人与海》
"The old man and the sea"!
从没听过
Never heard about it.
海明威关于人对抗自然的经典著作
Hemingway's classic tale of man versus nature.
让一个和上百只猫一起生活的人
Leave it to a guy with a hundred cats
去写个有关鱼的好故事 对吧
to write a good fish story, right?
哈哈 崔茜
Oh, ho, Trish!
这是在干嘛 读书俱乐部还是游戏
What is this, a book club or a fun game?
上
Go.
玩
Play.
五个单词
Five words.
第二个单词 吓 怕
Second word. Scared. Afraid.
-《谁怕弗吉尼亚·沃尔夫》 -对了
- "Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?" - Got it!
你太厉害了
You're amazing!
你都可以以此谋生了
Wowie! You could do this for a living.
真的吗 真的有这行吗
Really? There's such a thing?
不 就像也没有
No, just like there's no such thing
职业百老汇狂热粉丝一样
as a professional Broadway enthusiast.
你得找个正经工作
You're gonna have to get a real job.
好了 轮到我了
Okay, it's my turn.
我不知道这是什么
I don't know this.
我也不知道这是什么
妈 你拿到哪张就要演哪张
Mom, you have to do the one you pick.
不用 曼尼 没关系
Oh, no, Manny. It's fine.
慢慢挑吧 挑个你喜欢的
Just keep picking until you get one you like.
不 我用不着慢慢挑 我就要这张啦
No, no. I don't have to keep picking. I'm gonna do this one.
不 这个我可以
Uh-oh. No, I got this.
是戏剧 书 还是电影
Is it a play, a book, or a movie?
没错 其中之一
Yeah, one of those.
-《迷失》 -《独领风骚》
- "Lost"! - "Clueless"!
《年少轻狂》
"Dazed and Confused"!
真是太弱智了
This is stupid.
没人能猜得中
Nobody can get this.
你或许说的对 我...
You're probably right. I just...
就是啊 这是我写的 这个太难了
Yeah. See? This is one of mine. It's really hard.
真的吗 是什么 你试试
Really? What is it? You do it.
是戏剧
Play.
《理发师陶德》
"Sweeney Todd"!
答对了
Exactly.
真是最佳拍档
What a team.
这游戏蠢到家了
This is a stupid... game!
好 我在Facebook 推特等各大社交网站上
Okay, so after a quick scan of his Facebook, Twitter,
把他人肉了一遍
Tumblr, Pinterest, and Instagram,
得知如下情况
here is what I know.
这年头还有隐私可言吗
Privacy is dead?
他喜欢的有 芝加哥黑鹰队 跆拳道
Likes--Chicago Blackhawks, kickboxing,
《虎胆龙威》系列电影和啤酒
The movie "Die Hard," and beer.
-听起来像入过兄弟会 -他爱好多着呢
- He sounds like a frat boy. - Oh, he's many things.
他喜欢冥想 喜欢印第安菜
He meditates, he loves Indian food,
他超爱他的狗狗奥蒂斯
And he's crazy about his dog Otis.
这房子开了狗洞吗
Does the house have a doggie door?
-没有 -没有
- No. - No.
开一个 想拿下巴比 必先拿下奥蒂斯
Put one in. You get to Barbie through Otis.
她的搜查能力堪比《龙纹身少女》的女主角啊
She's like the girl with the dragon tattoo.
而且头发好看多了
With cuter hair.
-别吵吵 -她还真像啊
- Stop talking! - Oh, she really is.
那哥们喜欢穿黑色紧身衣的妹子
Dude has a thing for chicks in black tights,
他喜欢老式校园放克音乐
he likes old school funk,
而且踢球时踢蹦了门牙
and he chipped his front tooth playing soccer.
哎哟喂 真可爱
Aw! It's actually kind of cute.
天呐 你都爱上他了
Oh, my god. You're falling in love with him.
别闹 这是干正经事呢
Oh, please. It's just a job, nothing more.
好 足够拿下他了 行动吧
Okay, that's enough to go on. Let's move.
我们有两个小时
We've got two hours
来把这房子变成扎克·巴比的梦中豪宅
to turn that place into Zack Barbie's dream house.
-"芭比"的梦中豪宅 -我们没时间了
- Barbie's dream house. - We don't have time!
你刚刚闹的是哪出啊
What the hell was all that about?
你问崔茜去啊 她什么都知道
Why don't you ask Trish? She knows everything.
起码她不是个姘头啊
Well, at least she's not a bimbo.
她和曼尼挺玩得来的
She and Manny seem to hit it off fine.
你怎么了
What's the problem?
才一个周末 那孩子就迷上她了
Just one weekend, and he already idolizes her.
他怎么会不迷呢 她可比我聪明多了
And why wouldn't he? She's so much smarter than me.
她对他喜欢的东西了如指掌
She knows so much more about the things that he loves.
他俩有着外人听不懂的笑话
They have their little inside jokes.
要是她还会做他喜欢的卡布奇诺咖啡
If she learns how to froth his cappuccino,
我就彻底淘汰了
I am history.
你跟曼尼的亲密关系是我前所未见的
You and Manny have the closest relationship I've ever seen.
老天 除了你
Hell, he may never form
他不可能跟别的女人有这种健康的关系
a healthy attachment with another woman after you.
你真会哄我
You're just saying that.
曼尼喜欢她也没什么啊
And it doesn't matter if Manny likes her.
照哈维尔的作风
Knowing Javier's track record,
他肯定也会把她甩了的
He'll dump her like he dumps everybody.
你错了 杰 我不会甩她
You are wrong, Jay. I'm not going to dump her.
其实 这个周末 我向崔茜求婚了
In fact, this weekend, I asked Trish to marry me.
你要和她结婚
You're going to marry her?
我想着时机成熟就告诉你
I was waiting for the right time to tell you.
你"成功"了
Nailed it.
我想找你拿回我祖母的戒指
I wanted to ask you for my abuela's ring back.
我希望崔茜戴着它
I really want Trish to wear it.
她是我见过最好的女人
She is the most amazing woman I've ever known.
你看见我正拿着刀吗
You see that I am holding a knife.
得了吧
Please.
我们的婚姻中你有一半时间都拿着刀
Half our marriage was you with a knife.
崔茜就是我的归宿 曼尼已经喜欢她了
Trish is the one. And Manny already loves her.
他现在可以有更多时间跟我们在一起
He can spend more time with us now--
节假日 甚至暑假都行
Holidays, summers even.
好 我去给你拿戒指
Fine. I'll go get you the ring.
你欠我8美元
But you owe me $8
因为我把你所谓的"绿宝石"换掉了
Because I had to replace "The emerald."
哈维尔 你带过不少30多岁的"美酒"来我家
Javier, you've brought a lot of 30-year-olds around here,
但我最喜欢这回的
but this one's my favorite.
而且我也很喜欢崔茜
And I like Trish, too.
我也是
Me, too.
好 那我估计
Well, then I suppose this is
曼尼 现在是时候告诉你了
as good a moment as any to tell you, Manny.
我和崔茜要结婚了
Trish and I are getting married.
我的天 这真是最好的消息
Oh, my gosh. This is the best news ever!
来 喝一杯
Here. Drink.
亲爱的 听我说
Now listen, my love.
这是我祖母传下来的戒指
This belonged to my abuela.
哈维尔 现在可能不合适
Um, maybe not now, Javier.
不不 请听我说
No, no. Please. Please.
我真心希望 这枚戒指能戴在你的
It will fill my heart to see this ring on your...
纤纤玉手上
Your finger.
小了点儿哈
Oh. It's-- it's a little small.
我戴不了
I can't do this.
没事儿 我用点劲就是了
No, no. I'll just push a little harder.
哈维尔 别弄了 不可能的
Javier, stop. It'll never work.
等一下 宝贝
But wait, my love.
在你的手指上抹点黄油就行了
We can put butter on your finger.
他来了 开音乐
That's him. Hit it.
你好啊 不是他
Hey! Not him.
伙计们 抱歉我去了那么久
Hey, guys. Sorry it took me so long.
我以前从没买过啤酒 种类太多了
I've never bought beer before. There's just so many choices.
我们喝得了那么多吗
Do we really need that much?
不清楚 这些算多吗
I don't know. Is this a lot?
好戏开始了
Showtime!
你好啊 不是他
Hey! Not him.
大家好 我就是来看看情况如何了
Hey! Thought I'd just swing by and see how it's going.
扎克在吗
Zack here?
我的天
Oh, my God.
你穿了黑色紧身衣
You are wearing black tights.
艾丽克斯说得对 你就是喜欢他
Alex was right. You are into him.
那个荡妇佐伊伤透了他的心
That skank Zoey broke his heart.
我可以抚平他的伤痛
I can make him whole again!
海莉
Haley.
好了 这回该是他了
Okay, that has to be him.
我们自己家的人都已经在这儿了
Everyone we know is already here.
-大家站好位 不要出差错 -好
- Everyone, places. Let's make this perfect. - Yes.
我是艾拉·格拉斯
I'm Ira Glass.
-今天的节目 -不不
- Today on the program... - No, no.
-不是这个 -关掉
- That's not it.- Turn that off!
-不不不 -快关掉
- No, no, no, no, no! - Turn it off!
那是后退键
It's the back button.
你好啊 你一定是扎克吧
Hey! You must be Zack.
我是菲尔·邓菲 快请进
I'm Phil Dunphy. Come on in.
你好
Hi.
他们是我的同事
These are my associates.
-你好 晚上好 -你好
- Hello! Good evening. - Hi!
你好呀
Hi!
那位 是我女儿
Oh, and my, uh, my daughter.
就是这里啦
So... This is the place.
看起来不错
Looks nice.
扎克 你饿了没
So, Zack, you hungry?
没有 但是闻起来好香啊
Uh, no. But, uh, it smells great.
是从离这里不远的一个很棒的印度餐厅买的
Yeah, it's from this amazing Indian place just down the road.
走路就到了
It's walking distance.
那可真好
Which is awesome
就算你喝多了也没事 对吧
if you've had one too many brewskis, am I right?
是啊
Yeah.
有谁是黑鹰队的粉丝吗 我超爱黑鹰队
Oh. Is someone a blackhawks fan? Love the hawks.
是啊 那可真够巧的
Yeah, well, that's a weird coincidence.
我们去看看跆拳道健身房吧
Let's go check out the kickboxing gym.
真的吗 我正好练跆拳道
Seriously? I kickbox.
-不是吧 -真的
- What?! - Yeah.
走吧
Come on!
海莉
Haley!
崔茜 开门
Trish, open up!
不 我现在不想看见你
No. I don't want to see you right now.
开门 不然我踹门进来了
Open up, or I'm going to break down the door!
别冲动 那门可跟你无冤无仇
Hey! Hey, hey, hey! Don't break down the door!
见鬼
Ay, caramba.
我真该直接买个新戒指
I'm beginning to think I should've just bought a ring.
-让我和她谈谈 -你
- Let me talk to her. - You?
对 她吓到了 也许我能出点力
Yes. She's scared. Maybe I can help.
送她走远点 拜拜哟
Help her go... Adios.
去吧
Go ahead.
你告诉她 她现在头脑不清楚 很不理智
And you tell her she's being crazy and irrational.
如果她不出来 我就把这房子烧了
And if she doesn't come out, I'm going to burn down this house!
别烧我们家房子
Don't burn down the house!
崔茜 开开门 我是歌洛莉亚
Trish, open! It's Gloria.
抱歉 我想一个人静静
I'm sorry. I needed to be alone.
在曼尼的卧室里吗
In Manny's bedroom?
我之前以为这里是个卫生间
Well... I thought it was a bathroom.
有一股混合香料的味道
It smells like potpourri.
听我说
Listen,
我是最了解你现在这种
I would be the first person to understand that
犹豫要不要嫁给哈维尔的心情了
you're having second thoughts about marrying Javier.
确实
I am,
但我真的很爱他
but I do love him.
我知道你爱他
Of course you do,
尽管他这个人没有责任心 冲动任性
even though he's irresponsible and impulsive,
而且如果你的姐妹们有那么一丁点姿色
and if your sisters are even a little bit pretty,
-他都会 -不不不 不是这些
- he's gonna try-- - No, no, no, no, no. It's not that.
是因为他酗酒吗
Is it the drinking?
还是因为他好赌
Is it the gambling?
难道因为你手指粗吗
Is it because of your fat fingers?
-不 是因为你 -我
- No, it's you. - Me?
我怎么比得上你
How can I compete with you?
曼尼三句话不离
All Manny talks about
他有世界上最好的妈妈
is how he's got the world's greatest mom.
而且我知道哈维尔有多后悔失去你
And I know how Javier regrets losing you.
他才没有
No, he doesn't.
相信我 他有的
Oh, believe me, he does.
而我又怎么能怪他呢 你是这么的
And who could blame him? I mean...
瞧瞧你
Look at you!
谁能有这种傲人身姿
Who has a body like that?!
而且你两个月前才生了个宝宝
And you just had a baby two months ago?
你莫非是住在健身房吗
I mean, what--do you just live at the gym?
人家哪有空去健身房
Who has time for the gym?
你知道我午餐吃了什么吗
You know what I had for lunch?!
我只吃了半个燕麦棒
I had a half a granola bar,
但我还是扣不上裤子上的扣子
and I can't button my pants!
我不会做饭
I can't cook!
而且我的床上功夫撑死了算中等
And at best, I am average in bed!
我永远
And I will never,
永远不能达到歌洛莉亚女神的高度
ever, ever live up to the great Gloria!
欢迎成为我们家的一员
Welcome to the family!
话说你从花园后面
And did I mention that from the back of the garden,
可以看到拍摄《虎胆龙威》的
you can almost see a piece of the building
那栋楼的一角
that they shot "Die hard" in?
我有时候挺喜欢坐在那儿的
I like to sit back there sometimes.
那是一个整理思绪的好地方 还可以
It's a great place to gather my thoughts and just...
怎么说呢 静静沉思
I don't know. Be in the now.
我每天都会冥想
I meditate every day.
我的老天爷啊
Yippee-ki-yay!
怎么这么巧呢
What are the odds?
我这样说也许
You know, this is probably not gonna help
不利于还价 但是
my negotiating power, but...
我有点无法相信这房子的完美程度
I kinda can't believe how perfect this house is.
想想看 小奥蒂斯会多喜欢这道狗门啊
And how much is little Otis gonna enjoy this doggie door?
你怎么会知道我的小狗叫什么
How do you... know my dog's name?
我不知道
I don't.
你知道 你刚刚说了奥蒂斯
Yeah, you do. You just said "Otis."
不不 他说的是
No. No, no, he said,
噢 这道狗门会非常适合你的狗狗
"Oh, dis doggie door would be perfect for your dog..."
你应该有养狗吧
Should you own one.
-跟他说的完全不沾边 -我听到是这样
- That's not even close to what he just said. - That's what I heard.
总之 办第三方托管非常快
Anyway, we can do a very fast escrow
你到月底就能拿到这房子
and get you in this house by the end of the month.
正好可以赶上你的生日
Oh! Just in time for your birthday!
太诡异了
This is weird!
令我毛骨悚然
It's totally weird.
黑鹰队 你知道我的生日
Okay, the blackhawks, you know my birthday,
你知道我的狗叫什么
and you know my dog's name.
-我快被你们吓死了 -等等
- You guys are freaking me out. - Okay, wait a second.
我们对这间房子倾注了心血
We poured our hearts into this house,
我们只是想让你知道
and we just wanted to show you what it would be like
住这房子会是什么感觉
if you were living here.
我们稍稍过分了点吗
Did we go a tiny bit overboard?
我的天
Oh, my god.
我最喜欢的歌
Favorite song.
-做的"好" -慢走不送
- Way to go. - You take care.
这里到底能不能看到《虎胆龙威》的拍摄大厦
Can you even see the "Die hard" building from here?
不行
No.
我也会去科切拉音乐节 我会去找你的
I'll be at coachella, too! I'll come find you!
-宝贝 -海莉
- Honey! - Haley!
就这样了
Well, that's it.
我们正式完蛋了
We're officially screwed.
见鬼
Darn it.
没事的 亲爱的
It's okay, honey.
怎么没事 我有责任
No, it's not okay. I feel responsible.
我把大家拖下水的
I dragged us all into this.
这样做的目的就在于 我可以赚点小钱
The whole point was so that I could make a little extra money
对家里做点贡献
and contribute to the family,
结果呢 我却害我们赔钱
and instead, I'm gonna end up costing us.
我太失败了
I'm a failure.
别这样
Hey. Hey.
这种结果谁能预料到呢
No one could've predicted this.
我的错
My bad.
我们再找买家
We'll find another buyer.
-这次我们会吸取教训 -让我来
- This time, we'll learn from our mistakes. - Got it. I got it.
他回来了
He's back!
不不 别这样 别这样
No. No, no, no! Stop! Stop. Stop.
这是间不错的房子 是用正直打造的
This is a great house. It was built with integrity.
出售也要这样 不准再玩花样
We should sell it that way, okay? No more tricks.
-好 -我们要诚实
- Yeah. - Let's just be honest.
不玩花样
No tricks.
-邓菲 -格尔
- Hey, Dunphy. - Gil.
你公司的人说你在这里
Your office said you'd be over here.
对 我在这里
Yeah, I am here.
买家也在这里
With my buyers.
你们觉得怎么样
What do you guys think?
我的天 这房子太完美了
Oh, my god! This house is perfect.
我尤其喜欢客厅温馨的氛围
I especially love the warm embrace of the parlor!
-乐爆你的小心肝吧 -乐爆你的 宝贝
- It screams you. - No, it screams you, sweetie.
还是狗狗门 小卡 看啊
Oh, dis doggie door, Cam. Look. Ooh!
见鬼 同志伴侣
Damn it. Gays.
有他们准没好事
They come to play.
我没空 格尔
I'm busy, Gil.
在问我之前 别接受任何报价
Don't accept any offers without talking to me first.
我的客户想买 明白吗
My buyer wants in, all right?
不好说 买卖几乎敲定了
I don't know. We're pretty far down that road.
好吧 我们会提高价格
All right. We'll up the offer.
格尔
Gil...
我来告诉你事情会怎样
Let me tell you how this is gonna go down.
首先 你要请我共享温馨甜蜜的晚餐
First, you're gonna buy me a lovely dinner.
不 不对
No, that's not it.
首先 我要请你吃一顿温馨甜蜜的晚餐
First, I'm gonna buy you a lovely dinner.
然后我会带你去...
Then I'm gonna take you in the back...
成真了 成真了
It's gonna happen! It's gonna happen!
房子可以卖出去了
We're gonna sell the house.
你瞧 米奇尔 我早告诉你了吧
You see, Mitchell? I told you so.
我老婆 我要接电话
That's my wife. I better take it.
喂 听着 无论你说什么
Hey, hey. Whoa, listen. Whatever you do,
别跟她说你在工作日打高尔夫
don't tell her you're playing golf on a weekday.
否则今晚你就等着洗碗吧
You'll be doing dishes all night.
说的好 多谢了 我的男人
Good call. Thank you, my man.
亲爱的 什么事
Hey, honey. What's up?
不太忙
Oh, not much.
在开会
Just, uh, in a meeting.
努力工作 养家糊口
You know, working hard, bringing home the bacon.
他没有 他在打高尔夫
No, he's not! He's playing golf!
没有
No.
让开 一杆进洞
Um... Fore! Nice putt!
你为什么要骗你老婆 邓菲
Why you lying to your wife, Dunphy?
他中午还喝了啤酒
Hey, he had a beer at lunch, too!
你什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you?
你被我的"索"命鱼雷射中了吧
You just got thorpedoed!
回来
Come back here.